莉莉丝正试图破坏66个封印
Lilith is trying to break the 66 seals
从地狱解放路西法
To free lucifer from hell.
-你是谁?  -卡西迪奥
- Who are you? - castiel.
我是上帝的天使
I'm an angel of the lord.
安娜  你没事吧?
Anna,you all right?
我想起我的身份了
I remember now who i am.
我是一个天使
I'm an angel.
你跑不了的...迪恩
You can't run...dean.
阿拉斯泰尔
Alastair.
这位是尤利尔  一位专家
This is uriel,a specialist.
帕梅拉·巴恩斯  全国最好的灵媒
Pamela barnes,best damn psychic in the state.
帕梅拉!
Pamela!
他把我放下拷问台  之后我开始折磨其他灵魂
He took me off the rack,and i tortured souls,
而那时我很享受
And i liked it.
不管我拯救了多少人
No matter how many people i save,
都无法弥补这罪孽
I can't fill this hole.
我的问题不在于什么超能力
It's not the psychic thing i got a problem with.
我知道你的问题在哪儿
Yeah,i know what you got a problem with,
不过这很难
But tough.
-但却是唯一的办法  -不
It's the only way. no.
我知道你对那个恶魔做了什么  萨姆
I know what you did to that demon,sam.
帕梅拉!
Pamela!
永别了  我的姐妹
Goodbye,sister.
搞什么飞机?
What the hell?
露比会在怀俄明的夏延城和我们碰面
Ruby will meet us outside cheyenne.
她一直在追踪那几条线索
She's been tracking some leads.
听着  我知道你不喜欢她
Look,i know she's not exactly on your christmas list,
但她能帮我们找到莉莉丝
But if she can help us get to lilith --
老弟  我才不在乎和露比一起共事
Man,work with ruby,don't. i don't really give a rat's ass.
那你怎么了?
What's your problem?
帕梅拉本不想牵涉进来
Pamela didn't want anything to do with this,
是我们连累了她
And we dragged her back into it,sam.
她清楚这是存亡攸关的大事
She knew what was at stake.
是啊  拯救世界
Oh,yeah,saving the world.
而我们真他妈干得漂亮
And we're doing such a damn good job of it.
迪恩
Dean --
我再也不想埋葬伙伴了  萨姆
I'm tired of burying friends,sam.
听我说  如果我们抓到一条新线索
Look,if we catch a fresh trail --
我们就追踪下去  我懂
We follow it. i know.
但是我说了  我只是厌倦了
Like i said,i'm just -- i'm just getting tired.
化悲痛为动力吧
Well,get angry.
回家真"好"啊
Home,crappy home.
温彻斯特兄弟
Winchester and winchester.
不是真的吧!
Oh,come on!
我们需要你帮忙
You are needed.
帮忙?
Needed?
我们刚忙完回来!
We just got back from needed!
和我说话时放尊重点
Now,you mind your tone with me.
不  是你该放尊重点
No,you mind your damn tone with us.
我们刚从帕梅拉的葬礼上回来
We just got back from pamela's funeral.
帕梅拉  知道吗  那个通灵师?
Pamela -- you know,psychic pamela?
还记得她吧
You remember her.
卡西  你应该记得  你灼瞎了她的双眼
Cass,you remember her. you burned her eyes out.
还记得吗?  真是欢乐啊!
Remember that? good times!
之后她为了保护其中一个该死的封印而死
Yeah,then she died saving one of your precious seals.
你们能不能别再当我们小卒乱耍了
So,maybe you can stop pushing us around like chess pieces
哪怕一会儿也好!
For five freakin' minutes!
我们把你救出地狱自有目的
We raised you out of hell for our purposes.
好吧  什么目的?
Yeah,and what were those again?
你们到底想要我做什么?
What exactly do you want from me?
等你态度好些再说
Start with gratitude.
迪恩  我们明白这很难接受
Dean,we know this is difficult to understand.
但是我们...
And we...
我们可不在乎
...don't...care.
现在  已有7名天使被杀
Now,seven angels have been murdered --
他们都是我们的精英
All of them from our garrison.
昨晚又有一名天使被害
The last one was killed tonight.
是恶魔干的吗?
Demons?
它们怎么做到的?
How they doing it?
我们不知道
We don't know.
不好意思  就这件事我们能做什么?
I'm sorry,but what do you want us to do about it?
一个可以杀死天使的恶魔
I mean,a demon with the juice to ice angels
我们对他也无能为力吧?
Has to be out of our league,right?
我们能对付恶魔  不用你操心
We can handle the demons,thank you very much.
前提是我们要找到它们
Once we find whoever it is.
所以你要我们帮忙...
So,you need our help...
追捕恶魔吗?
Hunting a demon?
也不算是
Not quite.
我们抓到了阿拉斯泰尔
We have alastair. great.
他会告诉你们该找谁
He should be able to name your triggerman.
但他不肯说
But he won't talk.
阿拉斯泰尔的意志非常强大
Alastair's will is very strong.
我们的审讯陷入僵局
We've arrived at an impasse.
是啊  他可是拷问的专家
Yeah,well,he's like a black belt in torture.
你们的水平和他不能相提并论
I mean,you guys are out of your league.
那就是为什么我们来找他的高徒
That's why we've come to his student.
你恰好是
You happen to be
我们拥有的最称职的判官
the most qualified interrogator we've got.
迪恩
Dean...
你是我们最大的希望
You're our best hope.
不
No.
没门
No way.
你不能要求我做这种事  卡西  不要这样
You can't ask me to do this,cass -- not this.
谁说过...
Who said anything...
是要求你了?
about asking?
见鬼
Damn it!
这个恶魔陷阱是古老的魔法
This devil's trap is old enochian.
他完全被束缚了
He's bound completely.
精彩极了
Fascinating.
门在哪里
Where's the door?
你要去哪
Where are you going?
回去搭我的雪弗兰  谢谢
Hitch back to Cheyenne,thank you very much.
天使们在垂死挣扎  小子
Angels are dying,boy.
这些天每个人都在垂死挣扎
Everybody's dying these days.
你可以让我做任何你要求事
You can make me do whatever you want,
但是你不能让我做这件事
but you can't make me do this.
我知道要求你做这种事很难
This is too much to ask. I know.
但是我们必须要求你做
But we have to ask it.
让我单独和卡西聊聊
I want to talk to Cass alone.
那我想我可以去找找
I think I'll go seek...
启示录
revelation.
我们也许会有更进一步的要求
We might have some further orders.
出去的时候带两个甜甜圈回来
Well,get some doughnuts while you're out.
这小子就是不认输  是吧
Ah,this one just won't quit,will he?
我想我开始喜欢你了  小子
I think I'm starting to like you,boy.
你们这帮人走路太少  你们会变成病夫的
You guys don't walk enough. You're gonna get flabby.
你知道吗  我开始想
You know,I'm starting to think
我都比你们有幽默感
Junkless has a better sense of humor than you do.
尤利尔是天使卫队里最幽默的天使了
Uriel's the funniest angel in the garrison.
随便你去问
Ask anyone.
到底怎么了  卡西
What's going on,cass?
什么时候开始让尤利尔牵着你的鼻子走了
Since when does Uriel put a leash on you?
我的上司开始质疑我的同情心了
My superiors have begun to question my sympathies.
你的上司?
Your sympathies?
我和我管辖下的人类走得太近了
I was getting too close to the humans in my charge.
你
You.
他们认为我开始感情用事了
They feel I've begun to express emotions,
走上质疑上帝之路
the doorways to doubt.
这会削弱我的判断力
This can impair my judgment.
那就告诉尤利尔或是其他什么人...
Well,tell Uriel or whoever...
你不想让我做这事儿  相信我
...you do not want me doing this,trust me.
不想让你做?  是的
Want it? No.
但是我被告知我们需要你做
But I've been told we need it.
你要我打开那扇门走过去...
You ask me to open that door and walk through it...
你不会喜欢走回来的那个我的
you will not like what walks back out.
如果那是值得的话...
For what it's worth...
我愿放弃一切
I would give anything
让你不必做这事儿
not to have you do this.
天堂
Heaven.
我进天堂了吗
I'm in heaven ?
我的心太激动以至于口不能言
And my heart beats so that I can hardly speak
我仿佛找到了我的幸福之源
I seem to find the happiness I seek
当我们一起出去跳舞
When we're out together dancing
四目相对
Cheek to cheek.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我
I --
对你来说这是个极具戏剧性的重要时刻
This is a very serious,very emotional situation for you.
我真不应该笑
I shouldn't laugh.
我意思是说这事儿他们是认真的吗
It's just that,I mean,are they serious?
他们让你来折磨我
They sent you to torture me?
你只有一个机会
You got one chance.
就一个
One.
是谁在猎杀天使
Tell me who is killing the angels.
我要他的名字
I want a name.
你认为我看了你这些吓人的小玩具
You think I'll see all your scary toys
就会招供了吗
and spill my guts?
你总会招的  总有一个办法
Oh,you'll spill your guts,one way or another.
我只是不想弄脏我的鞋子
I just didn't want to ruin my shoes.
好吧...
Well...
现在回答我的问题
Now answer the question.
不然呢  你要玩儿死我吗
Or what? you'll work me over?
但是  也许...
But then,maybe...
你并不想那么做
You don't want to.
也许...
Maybe...
这是你的恐惧之源
you're a-scared to ?
我就在这里  不是吗
I'm here,aren't I?
不完整的你
Not entirely.
一部分的你留在了地狱
You left part of yourself back in the pit.
让我看看我们是否能
Let's see if we can...
帮你找回另一半  怎么样
Get the two of you back together again,shall we?
你会失望的
You're gonna be disappointed.
你还没让我失望过呢
You have not disappointed me so far.
来嘛
Come on.
我对你做了那么多
You got to want a little payback
你总想要点补偿的吧
For everything I did to you
让你遍体鳞伤的
For all the pokes and prods.
不要
No?
要不
Then...
说说我对你老爸做的事怎么样
How about for all the things I did to your daddy?
我还能闻到他们的气味
I can still smell them.
说实在的  萨姆  我又不是
Seriously,Sam,I'm not exactly dying
不和天使纠缠不清就会死
to tangle with angels again.
我要你查出他们把迪恩带去哪了
I need you to find out where they took dean.
我不太明白
Not sure I see the problem.
你知道他们抓住了阿拉斯泰尔
You know they have Alastair
用六芒星困住了阿拉斯泰尔
strung up six ways from sunday.
迪恩很了解他自己
Dean cuts himself a slice,
阿尔也已虎落平阳
Al's reduced to a quivering heap,
人人都会满意
And the good guys get the goods.
这又有什么问题
What's wrong with that?
他办不到
He can't do it.
听着  我明白
Look,I get it.
你不想让他再去拷问别人
You don't want him going all torture master again.
不  我是说  他办不到
No,I mean,he can't do it.
他完成不了这个任务
He can't get the job done.
在地狱里他经历了很多事  露比
Something happened to him downstairs,Ruby.
他不是以前的他了  他还不够强
He's not what he used to be. he's not strong enough.
那你呢
And you are?
我会变强的
I will be.
你爸爸被绑在刑架上差不多有一世纪
Had your pop on my rack for close to a century.
别再拖了
Can't stall forever.
约翰·温彻斯特  名字起的真好
John Winchester -- made quite a name for himself.
一百年啊
A hundred years.
每次用完刑
And after each session,
我都向他提出和你一样的要求
I'd make him the same offer I made you.
只要他接受  我就会停手
I'd put down my blade if he picked one up.
说出那个恶魔的名字吧  阿拉斯泰尔
Just give me the demon's name,Alastair.
但是
But...
他说  休想
He said,"nein"...
次次都这样
...each and every time.
他不向我妥协
Damned if I couldn't break him.
我就用尽办法折磨他
Pulled out all the stops.
但是约翰  他让有些事变得很特别
But John,he was... made of something unique.
英雄事迹啊
The stuff of heroes.
然后迪恩来了
And then came Dean.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Mmm,Dean Winchester.
我还以为我又碰上对手了
I thought I was up against it again.
但是爸爸的乖女儿
But daddy's little girl --
他妥协了
He broked.
他三十年就妥协了
He broked in 30.
你爸不希望你成为这种人吧  迪恩
Just not the man your daddy wanted you to be,huh,Dean?
现在
Now...
我们又重逢了
Now we're getting somewhere.
圣水
Holy water?
拜托
Come on!
小鬼  想打动我
Grasshopper,you're gonna have
也得有点创意啊
to get creative to impress me.
你知道吗  阿拉斯泰尔
You know something,Alastair?
就算是在地狱里  我也还有梦想
I could still dream,even in hell.
一次又一次  你知道我梦想什么吗
And over and over and over,you know what I dreamt?
就是梦想着这一刻
I dreamt of this moment.
相信我吧
And believe me...
我有办法让你说
...I got a few ideas.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
还想再要点吗
Let me know if you want some more.
还剩不少呢
There's plenty left.
去死吧
Go directly to hell.
不成功  便成仁
Do not pass go. do not collect $200.
Mihi pareas.
Ubicumque in occultatione sis,
Defigo te ut mihi pareas.
Igni...fiat...
Notum.
别紧张  火是我们的朋友
Relax. The fire is our friend.
再说了  我们只需要一部分地图
Besides,the only part of the map we need
就是"迪恩在哪里"的那部分
is the "where's dean" part.
有了
Out.
就在那  你哥哥就在那里
There. your brother is there.
天使们没把他们的肮脏交易藏着掖着
And it's a good thing angels aren't concerned
是件好事
with hiding their dirty business.
还没习惯被侦察
Not used to being spied on.
我是说  谁会傻到去试这个啊
I mean,who'd be stupid enough to try?
露比  好几个星期了
Ruby,it's been weeks.
我需要知道
I need it.
你好像不太高兴啊
You don't seem too happy about it.
你认为我想这么做吗
You think i want to do this?
这是我最不愿意
This is the last thing i --
但我需要够强
But i need to be strong enough.
没关系
It's okay.
萨姆  没关系的
It's okay,Sammy.
你可以拥有它
You can have it.
萨姆  没关系
It's okay,sam.
那就是小小恶魔刀
There's that little pig poker.
我还奇怪它到哪去了
I wondered where it went.
你真的以为这样可以拯救你吗
Do you really think this is gonna fix you?
给你一个终结吗
Give you closure?
那太可悲了
Oh,that is sad.
那可真可悲
That's really sad.
太可悲了
Sad,sad.
迪恩 是我重新塑造了你
I...carved you into a n-new animal,Dean.
没有回头路了
There is no...going back.
也许你说对了
Maybe you're right.
但现在轮到我来塑造你了
But now it's my turn to carve.
是谁控制着凶手
Who's behind the murders?
我要那个恶魔的名字
I want the demon's name.
安娜
Anna.
你好  卡西迪奥
Hello,Castiel.
你的人类身体
Your human body.
我知道它被破坏了
It was destroyed. i know.
但是
But...
我想我有点多情了
I guess i'm sentimental.
我想起了我以前得到一些帮助
Called in some old favors,and...
你不应该来这里
You shouldn't be here.
我们仍然有杀掉你的命令
We still have orders to kill you.
不知何故  我不认为你会那么做
Somehow,i don't think you'll try.
尤利尔在哪
Where's Uriel?
他去接受天启了
He went to receive revelation.
好吧
Right.
我真敬佩你的职业精神
Well,it's your professionalism that i respect.
你为什么要让迪恩这么干
Why are you letting Dean do this?
他在做上帝的工作
He's doing god's work.
折磨他人
Torturing?
那是上帝的工作吗
That's god's work?
卡西迪奥  住手吧
Stop him,Cass,please.
在你还没有毁掉自己真正的武器之前
Before you ruin the one real weapon you have.
我们怎么能去质疑上帝的指令呢
Who are we to question the will of god?
除非这不是他的指令
Unless... this isn't his will.
那这些指令从哪里来的
Then where do the orders come from?
我不知道  可能是一个像我们一样的人
I don't know. one of our superiors maybe.
但绝不是上帝
But not him.
谁在谋杀天使
Who's murdering the angels?
那个你爱的上帝
The father you love...
你觉得他想要这样吗
You think he wants this?
你觉得他会叫你这么做吗
You think he'd ask this of you?
你觉得这是正义的吗
You think this is righteous?
你现在的感觉
What you're feeling...
叫做怀疑
It's called doubt.
那些命令是错误的
These orders are wrong,
你明白的
And you know it.
但你能做正确的事
But you can do the right thing.
卡西迪奥  你害怕了
You're afraid,Cass.
我也会的
I was,too.
但如果我们一起
But together,we can --
一起
Together?
我和你没有共同点
I am nothing like you.
你堕落过
You fell.
离开这里
Go.
卡西迪奥
Cass.
离开
Go.
还不够强烈
Just not getting deep enough.
你缺乏手段
Well,you lack the resources.
事实是
Reality is just...
我不知道
I don't know.
具体不能在这说
...too concrete up here.
迪恩  说实话
Honestly,Dean...
你不明白它有多糟糕
You have no idea how bad it really was...
还有你对我们做了些什么
And what you really did for us.
闭嘴
Shut up.
迪恩  最残酷的事
The whole bloody thing,Dean.
莉莉丝最想要你去那里的原因
The reason Lilith wanted you there in the first place.
那我就让你闭嘴
Okay,then i'll just make you shut up.
不好意思
S-sorry.
有东西堵住了我的喉咙
Something caught in my throat.
我想是我的咽喉
I think it's my throat.
准备好
Well,strap in.
因为我才刚开始玩你
'cause I'm just starting to have fun.
本来应该是你父亲的
It was supposed to be your father.
本来应该有他来开启的
He was supposed to bring it on.
但最后  却是你
But in the end,it was you.
开启什么
Bring what on?
每晚  那一成不变的条件  还记得吗
Every night,the same offer,remember?
对你父亲开得也是一样的
Same as your father.
而终究还是你松了口  接受了
And finally you said,"sign me up."
还记得吗  你第一次拿起我的剃刀
Oh,the first time you picked up my razor,
你第一次
The first time
用剃刀扎进那个泪流满面的小贱人的那一刻
You sliced into that weeping bitch...
那就是第一道封印
That was the first seal.
胡扯吧你
You're lying.
古记写着  第一个封印打破之际
"and it is written that the first seal shall be broken
就是正义之士在地狱嗜血之时
"when a righteous man sheds blood in hell.
他的堕落  就是破印之源
As he breaks,so shall it break."
只有打破了第一个封印  其他的才能被打破
We had to break the first seal before any others.
就像是多米诺的原理一样
Only way to get the dominoes to fall right.
一定要推到最前面的那个才行
Topple the one at the front of the line.
当我们成功时
When we win...
重开天启之际
When we bring on the apocalypse
将地球变为炼狱那一刻
And burn this earth down...
其实这都拜你所赐
We'll owe it all to you...
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean winchester.
相信我  孩子
Believe me,son.
我没必要撒这种谎
I wouldn't lie about this.
这可关乎
It's kind of a...
我一直信奉的宗教信仰啊
...religious sort of thing with me.
不
No.
我知道你说的是真的
I don't think you are lying.
但纵然恶魔真得赢了
But even if the demons do win...
你也不会有命见证了
...you won't be there to see it.
你该找水管工好好看看那些管子
You should talk to your plumber about the pipes.
你还有很多东西要学呢  兔崽子
You've got a lot to learn,boy,
我会再送你回学堂好好调教的
So I'll see you back in class,
就从周一上午  晨光初洒的那一刻开始
Bright and early,monday morning.
哇哦  真够险的
Oh,almost.
看起来上帝是与我同在的
Looks like god is on my side today.
知道吗
You know...
你们天上来得家伙  就像小强一样难杀
Like roaches,you celestials.
我真希望能知道该怎么灭了你
I really wish I knew how to kill you.
不过至少我还知道要怎么把你送回你老家天堂
But all I can do is send you back to heaven.
Omnipotentis dei potestateminvoco.
东施效颦的蠢货
Stupid pet tricks.
究竟是谁杀了天使
Who's murdering the angels?
他们是怎么办到的
How are they doing it?
你真以为我会告诉你吗
You think i'm gonna tell you?
是的  我很肯定
Yeah,I do.
那些恶魔到底是怎么杀死天使的
How are the demons killing angels?!
我
I...
不知道
Don't...know!
好吧
Right.
不是我们干得
It's...not...us!
我们  没干过
We're...not doing it!
我可不信你你的鬼话
I don't believe you.
莉莉丝  根本不会这么做
Lilith... is not behind this.
她可不削只杀那么七个天使
She wouldn't kill seven angels.
她要杀就会成百
She'd kill 100...
上千的猎杀
1,000.
动手吧
Oh,go ahead.
不就是我送回去嘛
Send me back...
你也就那本事了
If you can.
我现在可不止那点儿本事了
I'm stronger than that now.
我可以直让你魂飞魄散
Now I can kill.
-萨姆  -到里面去把他治好
- Sam. -get in there and heal him.
-用神迹  快  -我办不到
- Miracle now. - I can't.
-是你和尤利尔把他害成这样的  -不是的
- You and Uriel put him in there! - no.
因为你们竟然连一个小小的恶魔陷阱都维系不了
Because you can't keep a simple devil's trap together.
我也不知道是怎么回事儿  那个陷阱
I don't know what happened. that trap --
不可能会出问题的  我很抱歉
It shouldn't have broken. I am sorry.
这件事从头到尾根本就是没事找事儿
This whole thing was pointless.
难道你还想不明白吗
You understand that?
那根本就不是恶魔干的
The demons aren't doing the hits.
而是别的东西让你们损兵折将的
Something else is killing your soldiers.
说不定是阿拉斯泰尔故弄玄虚呢
Perhaps Alastair was lying.
不
No.
他没有
He wasn't.
是卡西迪奥吗
Castiel?
我刚刚收到天使长传来的消息
I received revelation from our superiors.
我们的兄弟姐妹们正一个个地死去  他们
Our brothers and sisters are dying,and they --
他们希望我们俩将猎杀恶魔的事暂时搁置
They want us to stop hunting the demon responsible.
上面似乎出了什么乱子
Something is wrong up there.
你感觉到了吗
I mean,can you feel it?
凶手  可能并不是恶魔
The murderers -- maybe they aren't demonic.
萨姆·温彻斯特说
Sam winchester said
恶魔跟这个一点关系都没有
the demons have nothing to do with it.
如果不是恶魔  那会是什么
If not the demons,what could it be?
天堂的意愿
The will of heaven.
我们在失利  尤利尔
We are failing,uriel.
我们要打败仗了
We are losing the war.
可能战地已经被处罚了
Perhaps the garrison is being punished.
你认为我们的上帝会
You think our father would --
我觉得可能我们的上帝已经不再下达指令了
I think maybe our father isn't giving the orders anymore.
可能出了什么问题
Maybe there is something wrong.
好吧  我不想等着被消灭
Well,i won't wait to be gutted.
安娜
Anna.
安娜  拜托
Anna,please.
你最终还是决定杀了我么
Decided to kill me after all?
我一个人
I'm alone.
你想从我这得到什么  卡西迪奥
What do you want from me,castiel?
我在想着要不服从命令
I'm considering disobedience.
好
Good.
不  不是这样
No. it isn't.
自从第一次
For the first time...
我感觉到
I feel.
会越来越糟糕
It gets worse.
选择你自己行动的原因
Choosing your own course of action --
的确很让迷惑
It's confusing...
很恐怖
It's terrifying.
对
That's right.
你很好  用不上我的帮忙的
You're too good for my help.
我只是个垃圾
I'm just trash...
我是个活生生的亵渎上帝的家伙
A walking blasphemy.
安娜
Anna...
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
拜托告诉我该怎么办
Please tell me what to do.
就像以前一样么
Like the old days?
不
No.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
是时候你自己思考了
It's time to think for yourself.
你找我的
You called?
你怎么说  卡西迪奥
What do you say,castiel?
加入我吗
Will you join me?
还是跟我对战到底
Will you fight with me?
很奇怪
It's strange...
现在很奇怪
Strange how...
一根漏水的管子
A leaky pipe
就可以解除天使设的圈套
Can undo the work of angels
而我们自己
When we ourselves...
本应该是命运的使者
Are supppped to be the agents of fate.
阿尔斯泰尔比我们想象得更厉害
Alastair was much more powerful than we had imagined.
不
No.
没有恶魔能逃脱那个圈套
No demon can overpower that trap.
我自己做的
I made it myself.
我们做了很久朋友了  尤利尔
We've been friends for a long time,uriel.
并肩作战
Fought by each others' sides,
远离家乡  一同服役
Served together away from home...
太久了  似乎是
...for what seems like...
永远了
Forever.
我们是兄弟  尤利尔
We're brothers,uriel.
给我这个面子  告诉我真相
Pay me that respect. tell me the truth.
真相是
The truth is...
唯一能杀死天使的东西
The only thing that can kill an angel...
是另一个天使
...is another angel.
是你
You.
我想是的
I'm afraid so.
是你破了魔鬼圈套
And you broke the devil's trap,
把阿尔斯泰尔引到迪恩那去了
Set alastair on dean.
阿尔斯泰尔就不该是活着被囚禁的
Alastair should never have been taken aliv
真的很棘手  卡西
Really inconvenient,cass.
是的  我的确搞了点小破坏
Yes,i did turn the screw a little.
阿尔斯泰尔说不定已经杀了迪恩了
Alastair should' killed deanand,
并且你也谋害了我们的亲属么
For the murders of our kin?
不是谋害  卡西迪奥
Not murders,castiel.
不
No.
我的工作  就是转化
My work...is conversion.
我们在这等了多久
How long have we waited here?
我们又根据这些毫无意义的规则
How long have we played this game
玩这游戏玩了多久了
By rules that make no sense?
这是我们父亲的世界  尤利尔
It is our father's world,uriel.
我们的父亲
Our father?
他已经不是了  要是他真的曾是我们的父亲
He stopped being that,if he ever was,
他创造我们的这些的那一刻
The moment he created them.
我是说人性
Humanity.
他的最爱
His favorites.
他的牢骚  他恶心的幼虫
His whining,puking larvae.
你也要转化我吗
Are you trying to convert me?
我希望你能加入我  我还是这么希望的
I wanted you to join me,and i still do.
有了你  我们就足够强悍了
With you,we can be powerful enough to --
怎么
to?
净化我们的兄弟
to raise our brother.
路西法
lucifer.
你一定记得他
you do remember him.
他曾经那么强大
how strong he was...
那么的美丽
how beautiful.
他没有向人类卑躬屈膝
and he didn't bow to humanity.
他为了维护我们而被惩罚
he was punished for defending us.
如要你想要去相信什么
now,if you want to believe in something,cass,
把他作为你的信仰吧
believe in him.
路西法不是上帝
Lucifer is not god.
上帝不再是上帝了
god isn't god anymore.
他对我们不管不顾
he doesn't care what we do.
而我就是最好的证明
i am proof of that.
但是
but this?
你想要做什么 尤利尔
what were you gonna do,uriel?
你想杀了所有的精英么
were you gonna kill the whole garrison?
我只把那个说不的给杀了
i only killed the ones who said no.
其他人都已经加入我们了 卡西
others have joined me,cass.
兄弟  说真的  不要与我为敌
now,please,brother. don't fight me.
帮助我
help me.
帮助我把话传出去
help me spread the word.
和我一起召唤天启
help me bring on this apocalypse.
你所要做的
all you have to do...
只是勇敢些
is be unafraid.
那么久以来  这还是第一次
for the first time in a long time...
我真的无所畏惧
...i am.
尤利尔  你是赢不了的
you can't win,uriel.
我还是侍奉上帝
i still serve god.
你都没有见过上帝
you haven't even met the man!
没有意志
there is no will!
没有愤怒
no wrath!
没有上帝
no...god.
也许吧
maybe or maybe not.
但是还有我
but there's still me.
你没事吧
are you all right?
就算没事也不是因为你
no thanks to you.
你要加倍小心
you need to be more careful.
你要好好学下怎么困住恶魔
you need to learn how to manage a damn devil's trap.
我不是那个意思
that's not what i mean.
尤利尔死了
uriel is dead.
恶魔杀了他?
was it the demons?
是因为抗命
it was disobedience.
他跟我们对着干
he was working against us.
真的吗
is it true?
是我破坏了第一个封印吗
did i break the first seal?
是我导致了这一切吗
did i start all this?
是
yes.
当发现莉莉丝对你实施的计划时
when we discovered lilith's plan for you...
我们把地狱包围了
...we laid siege to hell,
我们想用自己的方式找到你  在你
and we fought our way to get to you before you --
开启天启之前
jump-started the apocalypse.
但是为时已晚
but we were too late.
为什么不直接把我留在那里
why didn't you just leave me there,then?
我不是责怪你
it's not...blame that falls on you,dean.
这就是命运的安排
it's fate.
开启这一切的义人(宗教用语)
and the righteous man who begins it
是唯一能阻止这一切的
is the only one who can finish it.
你必须阻止它
you have to stop it.
路西法?
lucifer?
天启?
the apocalypse?
什么意义
what does that mean?
你这狗娘养的  别再从我面前消失了
don't you go disappearing on me,you son of a bitch.
你到底什么意思
what does that mean?
我不知道
i don't know.
扯淡
bull!
真的
i don't.
迪恩  他们不会和我说的
dean,they don't tell me much.
我知道
i know...
你还有多少信仰
how our fate rests with you.
看样子  你们完蛋了
well,then,you guys are screwed.
我做不到
i can't do it,cass.
太沉重了
it's too big.
阿拉斯泰尔没错
alastair was right.
我不再是完整的我了
i'm not all here.
我不够强大
i'm not -- i'm not strong enough.
我不是那个人
well,i guess i'm not the man
我不是我爸爸想我成为的那个人
either of our dads wanted me to be.
找别人吧
find someone else.
我不是那个人
it's not me.